<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Mobile Tech Reviews - Reviews for Mobile &amp; Other Tech Related Things</title>
    <link>https://mobiletechreviews.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Mobile Tech Reviews - Reviews for Mobile &amp; Other Tech Related Things</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mobiletechreviews.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy S8 Plus Smart Review</title>
      <link>https://mobiletechreviews.github.io/post/samsung-galaxy-s8-plus-smart-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mobiletechreviews.github.io/post/samsung-galaxy-s8-plus-smart-review/</guid>
      <description>Samsung Galaxy S8 Plus is the best phone that will make you fall in love with it. In recent days it is the most trending phone in the mobile market you will find. It has larger screen size 6.2 inches compared to any phone launched in recent years. The other variant Samsung Galaxy S8 has a screen size of 5.8 inches. Both this phones are almost same in many aspects if compared.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Best Phone under Rs.10000</title>
      <link>https://mobiletechreviews.github.io/post/top-10-best-phone-under-rs-10000/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mobiletechreviews.github.io/post/top-10-best-phone-under-rs-10000/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I think that specifications of the phones just shows the one side of the coin, a great user experience matters more than great specifications. So, while reviewing this i have considered everything, the specifications, features, hardware, software (UI), real-world performance . As far as i am concerned i think that the user who is going to buy any phone as per his choice should be aware of the pros and cons of the phone i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Plus 5 Smart Review</title>
      <link>https://mobiletechreviews.github.io/post/one-plus-5-mart-sreview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mobiletechreviews.github.io/post/one-plus-5-mart-sreview/</guid>
      <description>OnePlus 5, reviewing this phone gives me lot of satisfaction as i am a big fan of OnePlus phones whether its any variant of One Plus. I must tell you buying this phone is worth for its price and you wont&amp;rsquo;t regret it. Last year the company had launced OnePlus 3T which made huge profit for the company almost in every country wherever it was launched. OnePlus 5 has launched two variant of OnePlus 5 that are OnePlus 5 6GB priced at Rs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>